<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moral Reminders</string>
    <string name="moralApp">Welcome to Moral Reminders!</string>

    <string name="quote1">We focus so much on our differences, and that is creating a lot of chaos and negativity and bullying in the world.
        And if we all focused on what we all have in common, which is we all want to be happy.</string>
    <string name="quote2">Bullying just shows one's insecurities.</string>
    <string name="quote3">Bullying creates character like nuclear waster creates superheroes. It's a rare occurrence and often does much more damage than endowment.</string>
    <string name="quote4">Victims of bullying spare themselves distress, by detachment; denying their ability to experience happiness.</string>
    <string name="quote5">Your pain may be the reason for somebody's laugh, but your laugh should never be the reason for somebody's pain.</string>
    <string name="quote6">You will never reach higher ground if you are always pushing others down.</string>
    <string name="quote7">Watch your thoughts, they become words. Watch your words, they become actions. Watch your actions, they become habits.
        Watch your habits, they become character. Watch your character, for it becomes your destiny.</string>
    <string name="quote8">Knowing what's right doesn't do much unless you do what's right.</string>
    <string name="quote9">Never do the wrong thing to make a friend or keep one.</string>
    <string name="quote10">Often the right part is one that may be the hardest for your to follow. But the hard path is also the one that will make you
        grow as a human being.</string>

    <string name="bully1">Never be bullied into silence, never allow yourself to be a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life; define yourself.</string>
    <string name="bully2">Don't take anything personally, nothing other people do is because of your, it is because of themselves.</string>
    <string name="bully3">How you make others feel about themselves says a lot about you.</string>
    <string name="bully4">A beautiful person is a person with a good heart, if you have a good heart, there is no way you can be ugly.</string>
    <string name="bully5">Our prime purpose in this life is to help others. And if you can't help them, at least don't hurt them.</string>
    <string name="bully6">What if the person you bully today, grows up and turns out to be the only surgeon that could save your life?</string>
    <string name="bully7">People who love themselves, don't hate others. The more we hate ourselves, the more we want others to suffer.</string>
    <string name="bully8">Life is like a fight, but not everyone's a fighter. Otherwise bullies would be an endangered species.</string>
    <string name="bully9">You should never make fun of something that a person can never change about themselves.</string>
    <string name="bully10">People try to say suicide is the most cowardly act a man could ever commit. I don't think that is true at all.
        What's cowardly is treating a man so badly that he wants to commit suicide.</string>

    <string name="feelGood1">We rise by lifting others.</string>
    <string name="feelGood2">Your are either as beautiful or as ugly as your feel you are. You define your beauty. That's not a power anyone can have over your.</string>
    <string name="feelGood3">The best way to cheer yourself up is to try to cheer somebody else up. -Mark Twain-</string>
    <string name="feelGood4">Smile often, think positively, give thanks, laugh loudly, love others, dream big.</string>
    <string name="feelGood5">Work hard and be kind, that is all.</string>
    <string name="feelGood6">You may go through a difficult time. Where you feel like a failure, but remember one thing,
        struggle and hard times are the most inspirational thing in the world.</string>
    <string name="feelGood7">Never lose your sense of wonder.</string>
    <string name="feelGood8">Compliment people. Magnify their strengths, not their weaknesses.</string>
    <string name="feelGood9">People who wonder whether the glass is half-empty or half-full are missing the point. The glass is half full.</string>
    <string name="feelGood10">It's ok to be a glowstick. Sometimes we need to break before we shine.</string>
</resources>
